-Hey, guys. -Hey.
-嗨！ -嗨！
-Hi. -Hey.
We need to talk about something.
啊，有点事和你们谈谈。
Yeah. We don't feel like we can host Thanksgiving this year.
我们觉得... 今年我们不能再作东感恩节晚餐了。
-What? -Are you kidding?
-什么，什么？ -什么，你是在开玩笑吧
Well, it's just with work and the stress of adoption..
嗯，由于工作，还有领养孩子的压力
we don't feel like we have the energy.
我们只是觉得没有精力弄了。
Plus, we don't think it's fair that every year the burden falls on us.
而且，每年都让我们受累，不公平。
That doesn't sound like you.
这不像你啊！
That's Monica talking.
这像是莫尼卡的话！
-No, we made this decision together. -She's putting words in your mouth.
-不，不，这是我们两个人的决定！ -这一定是她的意思！  （英文直译：莫尼卡把话语放在了钱德勒的嘴里）
Don't you put words in people's mouths. You put turkey in people's mouths.
你不应该把话送到我们口中 而是把火鸡送到我们口中……
I can't believe this. This is Emma's first Thanksgiving.
无法相信 这可是艾玛的第一个感恩节！
-No, it's not. -It's not? When was she born?
-不是... -不是？她什么时候出生的？
Well, personally, I think it's great you're giving yourself a break.
我个人认为，你们是应该休息一下子了。
-Thank you, Phoebe. -Sure. It's just as well.
-谢谢，菲比。 -不客气, 这样倒好
I mean, last year wasn't very good. I think she's losing her touch.
还有，去年的晚餐真好啊 她已江郎才尽，今年不会更好了。
-What? You are way off, lady. -Am I? Really? Am I?
-什么？你搞错了，女士！ -是么？
Well, why don't you cook Thanksgiving dinner and prove me wrong.
那你就再弄一次，证明我错。
Well, think about it. You'd be trying to top what you did last year.
你想想 你是在试图超过去年的顶峰
You'd be in competition with yourself.
你是在和...自己竞争！
That's my favorite kind.
真对我胃口！
Okay, we are doing this.
好吧，今年，我们继续！
Don't let yourself get manipulated this way.
别让自己这么容易被左右。
Stay out of this, Chandler. This is between me and me.
不关你的事，钱德 这是我和……“我”之间的事情！
We are supposed to make these decisions together.
我们应该一起决定啊！
Did you not watch the Dr. Phil I taped for you?
还记得费勒医生说的么？
The One With The Late Thanksgiving
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
-Hey. -Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
-嗨 -嗨，感恩节快乐！
Happy Meatless Turkey-Murder Day.
耶，火鸡殉难日快乐！
You guys, I ordered some chocolate pies from that bakery on Bleeker.
我订了些巧克力派
-Could you pick them up for me? -You're not making the pies?
-你们能帮我去取过来么？ -你不自己作派吗？
I don't make chocolate pies.
不，我不做巧克力派的。
When I was younger, I entered this pie-eating contest.
我小时候参加过一个吃派比赛
I ate so many that the thought of them makes me sick.
吃的太多了，导致我一想就恶心。
Did you at least win the contest?
那你赢了没有？
Two minutes, twelve pies and a part of one tin.
两分钟吃了12个外加一罐！
-Okay, I'll see you guys at 4. -Can't wait.
-好吧，我们4点见。 -很让人期待哦！
This dinner is gonna be so great. In your face, last-year me.
去年的莫妮卡, 我要你好看！
-Hey, Rach? -Yeah.
-嗨，瑞秋 -嗯？
What's Emma doing today?
艾玛今天有事么？
Well, let's see, I know that she has a meeting with her lawyer..
嗯，她啊，我只知道她今天要和律师见面
and then she has to make a very big poop.
然后做一个重大的决定。
-Why? -I want to enter her in a baby pageant.
-怎么了？ -嗯，我想让她参加婴儿选美。
Oh, my God. That's the creepiest thing I've ever heard.
哦，天哪，这是我听说过的最奇怪的事情。
Okay, but before you say no, my friend Suzanne is entering her kid.
我朋友苏珊带她的孩子参加了
And compared to Emma, she's a real dog.
和艾玛比起来，那小家伙就像只小狗！
-Phoebe, all babies are beautiful. -Oh, okay.
-哦，菲比，所有孩子都是美丽的！ -好吧
No. Phoebe, just the idea of pitting one baby against another..
菲比，难道我们只是为了一个奖杯
I mean, you know, and judging who's cuter just for a trophy..
就把孩子们比来比去，决定谁更漂亮么？
-And a thousand dollars. -is something I'm very interested in.
-一千美金。 -对此我很感兴趣！
Oh, please, do not tell Ross.
对了，别告诉罗斯。
He still believes that what's on the inside is important.
他始终不信任那些内部的...
Okay. And Emma needs a cowgirl outfit for the competition.
对了，艾玛得穿牛仔装！
Where am I gonna get a cowgirl outfit on Thanksgiving?
感恩节我上哪儿找牛仔装啊？
Well, I was thinking..
让我想想……
Take the clothes off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid!
把乔伊的菜地娃的衣服扒了！
Did someone drop the baton again?
又有人把指挥棒给掉了？
Why come all the way from Kansas to do that?
为什么每次都是堪萨斯的？
I don't get older, I just get better.
我不是越来越老，而是越来越好！
You know what just occurred to me?
你知道我刚想到什么？
This could be our last Thanksgiving just the two of us.
这可能是最后一次 只有我们两个人一起过感恩节了。
I mean, we could be getting a baby soon.
我觉得，我们很快就会有个孩子了！
-You don't know that. -Somebody's gonna pick us.
-你怎么知道？ -有人会选择我们的。
But we haven't heard a thing from the adoption agency.
可是这几周我们都没收到领养消息！
I'm telling you, it's gonna happen.
我敢保证
Next year, it's gonna be you, me and little Hemingway Bing.
明年会是你、我、还有海明威--宾！
-What? He's my favorite author. -Name one of his books.
-……嗯，因为他是我最喜欢的作家。 -说出他一本书的名字。
The Firm?
《企业》？
Okay, let's see. Okay, the turkey's in the oven. The stuffing is ready.
好吧，火鸡已经在烤箱里了 填料也准备好了。
You know, you always cook this meal all by yourself. Let me help this year.
你知道么，你总是自己弄这些东西 今年让我帮帮你吧。
Oh, Chandler, that's sweet.
哦，钱德，这太好了！
But you don't have to do everything Dr. Phil tells you to do.
但你不用一直按费尔医生说的作
I'm serious, let me do something. Just not the turkey. Nothing high-profile.
我是认真的。让我做点什么吧 不是火鸡，也不是填馅，做点不难的东西。 .
Okay, let's see. Oh, the cranberry sauce.
我想想……啊，酸梅酱！
It's easy to make, and no one really cares about it.
容易做，而且大家也不是很在意那东西！
Tell me more.
说来听听？
I'm gonna go check on something across the hall. You start by washing these.
我去对门儿检查别的 你先把这个洗干净吧。
Not with soap!
别用洗涤剂！！
You obviously haven't tasted my Palmolive potatoes.
你肯定没吃过我做的烤土豆……
-Hi. Hey, guess what Joey has. -Three tickets to today's Rangers game!
-嘿，猜猜乔伊拿到了什么？ -三张今天纽约游骑兵的票（美国冰球大联盟NHL）！
Dude, I wanted him to guess.
兄弟，我是让他猜的！
-Oh, my God. -Yeah, they're great seats too.
-哦，天哪！ -是啊，而且是好座位哦！
-Guess where they are. -Center ice.
-猜猜什么位置？ -正中间！
Did I do something to you?
我是不是和你有什么过节？
-The game's at 1. -So?
-嗯，比赛一点开始。 -怎样？
-Dinner's at 4. We'll never make it back. -So we'll leave before it's over.
-晚饭4点开始，我们赶不回来的。 -那我们就提前退场，这样时间就够了。
But it could take us a long time to get back home.
你现在这么说，可是到时候必定 要花很多时间回来的
Plus, Joey could get lost and they could have to page us to go pick him up.
另外 乔伊可能会迷路，还得把他领回来。
Dude, two times that happened!
老兄，事不过三！
Look, Monica's been working hard all day.
莫尼卡为了做晚饭忙了一整天
She didn't want to host in the first place. We shouldn't go.
她希望她的晚餐最重要，我们不该去的。
He's right, man.
他说得没错儿
-Yeah, I guess. So we'll see you at 4. -Okay.
-好吧。那么四点钟见。 -嗯
And get ready to taste my very special cranberries.
准备好品尝我的特制酸梅酱哦！
Or should I say "Chan-berries"?
或者，应该叫做“钱梅”...
That's some gentle comedy, dude.
伙计，又不是在演轻喜剧
-We're still going to the game, right? -Yeah.
-我们要去看比赛吧？ -是的！
This is contestant number 16, Rebecca Hope from Yonkers.
这是16号运动员 来自杨克斯的Rebecca Hope
-Hey. -Phoebe, listen, I think we gotta go.
-嘿！ -菲比，我想走了
This place is freaking me out.
这地方让我坐立不安。
I've been watching this guy over there. I don't think he came with a kid.
你看到那边那个人了么 我可不认为他带来的是个孩子！
But we can't leave now.
但我们现在不能离开啊
There was this one baby, Haley, who was favored to win..
最被看好的那个孩子Haley
she got croup, so she had to stay home.
因为感冒不能来
This competition just blew wide-open, folks.
竞争才刚刚开始哦！
Phoebe, it's just too weird.
菲比，这太奇怪了
I just saw a 1-year-old with pantyhose on.
我看见一个一岁的小孩穿连裤袜！
Oh, I know. We should've been more prepared.
哦，我就觉得我们准备不够充分
It's okay. Now, the way I see it, our real competition now is Cameron.
我觉得，咱们最有力的竞争对手是卡米隆。
My God, they just took her sweater off.
哦，天哪，她的衣服被脱掉了
Look at those arms. Hello, Michelin Man.
看她的手臂，就像...米其林 （著名轮胎的卡通形象，绿色滴~~）
Phoebe, come on. You know what, it's already 3:00.
菲比，已经三点钟了 而他们还没有评审到艾玛这一组
They haven't even gotten to Emma's group yet. We got dinner.
我们该走了，回去吃饭。
But Emma's got what it takes. She could go all the way!
但艾玛今天肯定能赢
-Phoebe, you have to calm down. -Okay.
-菲比，冷静点。 -好吧，
Rachel, the hottest babies in the tri-state area are in this room right now.
瑞秋，现在 这附近最漂亮的宝贝们都在这里了。
I overheard a judge say that not one of them holds a candle to Emma.
而我听见一个评审说 没人比得过艾玛。
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的么？ -没错！
-You heard him say that? -Yeah.
-你听见他们这么说？ -对。
All right. Okay. All right, let's give these babies something to cry about.
好吧，那就让我们 给其他的孩子们一点悲惨的回忆！
Good. Let's get down to business. Emma needs some makeup.
太好了，开工吧！艾玛需要化妆。
What?
什么？
She's gonna look washed-out next to the others.
她应该比其他孩子看起来更漂亮！
No, I'm not letting you put makeup on my baby.
菲比，我不会让你给我的孩子化妆的！
-Why not? -Because I already did.
-为什么不？ -因为我已经给她化过了！
You suck! Get off the ice, you idiot!
鲍伯，干掉那家伙！
-What a game. -I know. Yeah.
-太精彩了！ -没错，耶！
-I can't believe Chandler's missing this. -I'm sorry he's not here.
-真遗憾钱德错过了这场比赛！ -我也替他觉得遗憾
But I gotta say, I am really enjoying nacho chair.
但我要说的是，我真的很喜欢这个“玉米片”座！
Yeah, I'd probably enjoy it more if you didn't keep batting my hand away.
嗯，要是你不总是把我的手打开， 我可能也会吃不少呢
-Yeah! -These seats are great.
-哦！ -这位置太棒了！
I know, I know. When I was here for "Holidays on lce"..
是啊，没错！ 上次假期我在这看比赛，座位太远了
I was sitting so far away, Michelle Kwan couldn't read my banner.
关颖珊（花样滑冰世界冠军）根本就看不到我举的条幅。
Dude, I'm sure she knows you heart her.
老兄, 我认为她知道你心里有她
I hope so.
希望吧
We'd better get going. If we don't leave now, we're gonna be late.
嘿，我们该走了啦，回去吃饭。
But it's a tie game. So we're a little late. The girls will be there.
可比赛太精彩了！ 我们可以晚回去点吧，女生们应该准时的
Let's just stay for one more goal.
再进一个球再走啦
-I don't know. -One more fight.
-不好吧.. -再进攻一轮？
-Okay. -Okay.
-好吧。 -好吧。
Where is everybody? They're 45 minutes late.
大家都哪里去了？他们迟到了45分钟！
I can't believe they're not here. I slave and I slave for what?
我不相信他们会不来！我辛苦了一天 而我这么辛苦是为了什么？
They've ruined Cranberry Day.
他们毁了我的酸梅日！
-How late are we? -Forty-five minutes.
-我们迟到了多久？ -45分钟
-Here. -Okay.
-给. -好的.
Rachel and Phoebe are already there, so they probably started without us.
瑞秋和菲比应该已经到了 也就是说她们应该已经开始了
We could just slip in, and no one needs to know where we were.
让我们溜进去，这样谁都不会注意我们的。
-You may want to lose the foam finger. -Oh, no, no, no.
-你不把这个泡沫大手指扔掉么？ -哦，才不呢！
You just want to put it on your hand.
我知道你想抢走他！
-You're not at Thanksgiving? -No, we're late.
-你们没在里面？ -不，我们迟到了！
-What are you doing here? -We're late too.
-你们在这里干什么？ -我们也迟到了！
We figured we could be late because you'd be on time.
我们本以为你们不会迟到的！
Don't point that thing at me, Tribbiani.
别用这个指着我，崔比阿尼！
-Nobody's here? Monica's gonna kill us. -Yeah, where were you?
-那...里面没人，莫尼卡会杀了我们的！ -你们到什么地方去了？
-Well.. -Yeah, what's with the trophy?
-啊… -那是什么奖杯？
Well, we were at a spelling bee.
嗯，我们去参加拼字大赛了。
And I won.
我赢了！
You won an adult Thanksgiving Day spelling bee?
你在感恩节这天 赢得了一场成人拼字游戏？
Yes. Y-E-S. Yes.
是-的, 是的！
Let me see this. "Grand Supreme Little Darling, New York Division"?
让我看看…… 超级小可爱，纽约区。
That's me.
那便是我！
You entered Emma in a beauty pageant?
你们让艾玛参加了选美比赛？
And it looks like she put makeup on her.
而且还给她化了妆！
Wait a second. Where have I seen that cowgirl outfit before?
等等，等等 我好像在什么地方见过这身牛仔...
I can't believe this. She's our daughter.
无法置信，她是我们的女儿！
That you would treat her like some kind of show dog is inexcusable.
你把她当成观赏狗一样，不可饶恕
-She won a thousand dollars. -So this is an annual thing?
-她为我们赢得了一千美元！ -啊，是一年一次的吗……
That's Alicia May Emory's outfit!
啊，这是Alicia Mae的装备！
Guys, there are people in there who are not getting any happier.
伙计们，有人在里面要发火了！
-What are we gonna do? -I gotta put Emma down for a nap.
-天哪，我们该怎么办？ -我不知道，你们想吧, 我先把艾玛送回去。
And, Rach, while you're in there, throw something on Alicia May.
哦，瑞秋，至少给个主意吗
-All right, what are we gonna say? -We'll say that we were mugged.
-我们该怎么说？ -我们可以说，我们被抢劫了
You can't get mad at someone who's been mugged.
当有人被抢了的时候，是不能生气的！
Good. But you don't look like you were mugged.
嗯，不错，但你看起来不像被抢过。
No. Here.
不像..这样才像
Hey!
嘿！
Do you hear something?
你有没有听到什么？
-They're out there. -Let me see.
-他们都在外面！ -让我看看！
I can't believe this. They're an hour late, and they're just standing there talking.
我真没办法相信，他们迟到了一小时 还在那里聊天！
Everything's so distorted. It looks like Joey has a giant hand.
一切都乱套了，乔伊有只大手！
That says "Rangers" on it. They went to the game.
上面写“游骑兵”，他们去看比赛了！
Oh, they are in for a world of pain.
哦，这太可怕了！
-Ross' shirt is torn. -They're late and they're sloppy.
-罗斯的衬衫撕坏了。 -他们不但迟到，而且衣衫不整！
All right, Emma's napping. What happened to your shirt?
好了，艾玛睡下了。你的衬衫怎么了？
I got mugged, and they stole my pocket.
我被抢了，他们还偷走了我的钱包。
We're just trying to figure out an excuse.
瑞秋，我们是在找借口。
How about this?
好吧，想想
We could say that Monica told us 5:00, not 4:00. That way we're right on time.
我们可以说，莫尼卡告诉我们是5点 而不是4点，所以我们没迟到，我们是准时的！
Or we could plant PCP in the apartment and call the cops on her.
或者, 我们可以在房间里放些迷药，布个局！
That would be a good way to get rid of all the PCP we have lying around.
嗯，这的确是个下迷药的好办法。
We'll just say that she said it was 5:00.
你可以就说她说的是5点
We'll just act casual. We're not late, we're right on time.
做得自然些 所以我们根本没有迟到！
"We know you're out there."
“我们知道你们在外面。”
Who do you think it's from?
你觉得这是谁写的？
Oh, God, this is bad. This is so bad.
哦，太糟了，太糟了。
Well, let's just go in there and face them.
好吧，让我们进去面对他们吧。
I'm not going in first. I bet that vein on Monica's forehead is popping like crazy.
我不要先进去 莫尼卡生气的面孔会让我发疯的。
I hate that thing. It's like a bolt of lightning.
嗯，我也不要 那张脸就像扭曲的闪电一样……
Why don't we play Rock, Paper, Scissors, and whoever loses, goes in first.
嘿，我有主意了 我们可以玩石头剪子布，输了的先进去！
-All right, I'm in. -Ready.
-好吧，开始吧。 -准备好了么？
I win.
啊，我赢了！
-What is that? -That's fire. It beats everything.
-这是什么？ -火焰，赢过一切！
Oh, really? Does it beat water balloon?
真的么？能赢过一个水球么？
Well-played, Phoebe Buffay. Well-played.
好极了，菲比，玩得真好。
All right, let's all go in at the same time.
好啦好啦，让我们一起进去算了。
-Okay. -Okay.
-好。 -好。
-It's locked. -What? Oh, sure, now they lock it.
-锁住了！ -哈，他们把门锁上了
When they're having sex on the couch, it's like:
等他们在躺椅上 准备嘿咻的时候，他们就会说
"Come on in, my butt is surprisingly hairy!"
“啊，快进来，快进来，我等不了了！”
All right, come on. All right, you guys, we're so sorry we're late.
好吧。伙计们，你们怎么样啊？ 很抱歉我们迟到了
Please let us in so we can have dinner together.
让我们进去一起吃晚餐吧！
No, everything's cold. The turkey's dried out and the stuffing's all soggy.
不，东西都凉了 火鸡干了，馅也松了！
Yeah, and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that's..
嗯，而且那碗酸梅酱也……
What happens to cranberry sauce?
酸梅酱怎么了？
-Nothing, it's fine. -Oh, thank God.
-没事儿，很好。 -哦，谢天谢地。
Come on, you guys, we're sorry. Our subway broke down.
好啦，伙计们 真的抱歉，我们的车坏了。
That's a lie! You went to the game. I can see Joey's hand.
说谎！你们去看比赛了 我能看到乔伊的手！
For the love of God, take it off!
我说过了让你把它扔掉了！
Guys, it doesn't matter why we're late. We're all here now.
伙计们，我们是否迟到了并不重要 重要的是我们都到了
Please let us in so we can have some of your delicious turkey.
让我们进去吃美味的火鸡吧！
I had a dream once about a fax machine that did that.
我做梦都在想啊，这是什么？
That's all the turkey you're gonna get.
这就是你们该得的火鸡！
-How are we gonna decide who gets this? -Water balloon!
-怎么决定谁吃？ -水球！
What are we gonna do? I'm starving.
我们该怎么办啊，我饿死了！
I just remembered, we do have something to eat.
哦，对了，我想起来了
Monica put something in our oven this morning.
今天早晨莫尼卡放了点东西在炉子里面！
You touch that, and you will be sorry!
嘿，动了它你会后悔的！
Guys, I'd listen to her. The vein is bigger than I've ever seen it!
大伙, 最好听她的 她的血管涨到前所未有的大
Oh, my God, it's Brussels sprouts!
天哪，是甘蓝菜！
That's worse than no food.
这是什么嘛，不能吃的！
All you got was Monica's stinky Brussels sprouts.
啊哈，你们喜欢莫尼卡的发臭的甘蓝菜么？
Stinky?
发臭的？
Please let me stay on this side of the door.
请让我呆在这一边……
Oh, I know! I still have my old key.
对了，我还有以前的钥匙呢。
We can just unlock the door.
我们可以直接把门打开！
I don't know if that's a good idea. They don't wanna be with us.
我不觉得这是个好主意 他们明显不想和我们在一起。
I don't wanna be with them either..
你知道么，我也不想和他们一起
but it's Thanksgiving, and we should not want to be together together.
但今天是感恩节，不想在一起也要在一起！
If I could just get in there, make a face-to-face apology..
让我们进去面对面的道歉吧
look them in the eye, I could get them to forgive us.
看到我的眼睛，他们就会原谅我的。
-I don't know. -I'm telling you..
-我不懂。 -我来告诉你……
I can do it.
我做得到。
Yeah, he can do it.
嗯，你做得到。
It all looks so beautiful.
啊，太美了！
-The turkey, the stuffing. -The cranberries.
-那火鸡，那填料…… -那酸梅呢？
Enough! A monkey could've made them.
够了，猴子都会做！
Hey, listen, guys, we feel really terrible.
嘿，听我说，我们真得很抱歉……
He's doing that weird eye-contact thing.
他又来那什么“目光接触”了
Don't look at him. Don't look at him.
别看他，别看他。
Come on, you guys. We want you to know we're very, very sorry.
听我说，伙计们，我们想让你们了解 我们真的，真的很抱歉……
Right, guys?
对吧，伙计们？
-I feel terrible. -Oh, so sorry.
-真的很抱歉 -非常，对不起……
But let's not ruin this day. You've worked so hard.
别让我们毁了这一天，你们如此的辛劳！
Let's move past this and try to have a nice meal all together, huh?
让我们忘了这件事，一起吃饭吧！
The floating heads do make a good point.
那些漂浮着的脑袋好像说的没错。
Yeah, they do seem to feel pretty bad.
是啊，他们真的好像很抱歉。
-So bad. -So bad.
-对不起，对不起…… -对不起，对不起……
Okay.
好吧
Okay, you two go get the dessert, and I'll let you in.
好吧，你们两个去拿甜品来 我让你们进来。
Dessert?
甜品？
Yeah, I asked you and Phoebe to pick up the pies. You did remember, right?
是啊，我让你和菲比去取派 你记得的，对吧？
Pies. Oh, we thought you said "prize."
派？啊，我们以为是“奖”！ (注：英语中“派”和“奖”发音相同。）
Here.
这个！
-"Grand Supreme Little Darling"? -Congratulations!
-超级小可爱？ -恭喜！
Oh, my God, you forgot the pies? Well, I cannot believe this.
天哪，你忘了拿派？无法置信！
You forced me to make dinner, you're an hour late..
你们强迫我做饭，又迟到一小时
and you forget the one little thing that I asked you to do.
居然还忘记了我拜托你们做的一点点小事！
Really, girls, not cool.
真的，女孩子们真冷酷。
Well, you man-heads aren't any better. You lied about going to the game.
好吧，你们男人又好到哪里去？ 你们说谎，去看比赛
You knew it'd make you late, and you went anyway.
明知道会迟到，还坚持要去。
Hey, I'm getting a little tired of this. We said we're sorry.
我有点烦了。我们都道歉了
It's Thanksgiving, for Pete's sakes! A day of forgiveness.
今天是感恩节，是原谅之日！
-It's a day to be thankful. -Don't make me come up there!
-是感谢之日吧…… -别和我唱反调！
It's too late for apologies.
现在道歉太晚了！
Fine, let's just go. I don't need your stupid dinner.
好吧，我们走，我们可以不在这里吃饭！
That would be a lot more convincing if you weren't drooling.
如果你们开玩笑的话，可能更可信点。
-Oh, is that what that is? -Sorry.
-哦，我们现在就不是么？ -对不起
Come on, you guys, let's just do our own Thanksgiving.
伙计们，我们自己准备感恩节晚餐吧！
-Yeah, I'll cook. -Yeah, let's go out.
-好，我做饭！ -好，走吧！
Yeah, you three have a nice Thanksgiving.
你们三个，感恩节快乐！
-The three of us? -Yeah. You, Chan and the vein.
-三个？ -你，钱德，还有“白忙活”！
-I'm stuck. -Joey, that is not gonna work.
-啊，我被卡住了！ -乔伊，少来！
No, seriously.
不，我是认真的
-I'm really wedged in here. -I'll pull you through.
-我真的被卡住了 -我把你拖过来
Okay.
好。
Stop, stop, I'm worried about damaging my head.
啊，住手，住手 我担心会弄伤我的头！
It's a little late for that.
已经晚了
Hurry up, you gotta do something.
快点，帮帮忙啊！
All right, well, this does not change anything.
这不会改变什么的！
We need to get something to grease his face.
我们需要点能增大空隙的工具。
-We got turkey grease. -Bring it.
-我们有火鸡汁！ -拿来。
I just want to say that I'm sorry I referred to the vein as a separate person.
我很抱歉，我把“白忙活”算作一个人
Here you go.
拿来了。
Oh, that smells good.
啊，味道不错
-Okay? -Okay, try it.
-好了吗？ -好，试试看。
It isn't working.
没用！
-We're gonna have to unscrew the chain. -Hurry, I can't feel my ears.
-把链条卸下来吧。 -快点，我都感觉不到我的耳朵了！
Can you ever feel your ears?
你曾经感觉到过耳朵么？
Interesting.
嗯，很有趣。
-Chandler, where are your tools? -Oh, I left them on my bulldozer.
-钱德，你的工具哪里去了？ -啊，我把它们放在别的地方了。
I don't have tools.
我没有工具。
-Well, I do, but Rachel borrowed them. -I lent them to Ross.
-我有，但被瑞秋借去了。 -我借给了罗斯。
-I gave them to Joey. -I left them at the park.
-我给了乔伊。 -我留在车库了。
I'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.
这还真麻烦。
I stuffed Brussels sprouts down his pants.
我早就已经被他裤子里的甘蓝菜味道弄晕了。
Nice.
很好。
Okay, I have to get that.
好，我去接电话
Now, when I get back, I want you and your friends to be gone.
当我回来的时候 我希望你和你的朋友们已经离开了。
Thanksgiving is over. The vein has spoken.
感恩节完了！这是“白忙活”说的！
-It's really starting to hurt. -Look, I'm gonna pull on the door..
-我的头真的被卡住了！ -好吧，我会拉门
and you guys push. Maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out, okay?
然后你们努力推 这样他就有足够的空隙出来了，好吧？
Okay, so push.
好，推吧！
Just a sec. We're kind of in the middle of something here.
啊，等下，我们正忙着……
Hey, stop putting things down my pants.
别往我的裤子里面放东西！
-Come on, guys, push! -Yeah, come on, push!
-来吧，伙计们，推吧！ -来，推，推，推！
Push! Push!
推，推！
-My cranberries! -Man, I got food all over me.
-我的酸梅！ -我全身都是！
I can't believe what you did. Monica's gonna kill you.
惨不忍睹，莫尼卡会杀了你的！
Look! Look! Look what the.. Look what the floating heads did!
看，看，看 这个“漂脑袋”作了什么？
I don't care.
没关系。
What's going on?
怎么了？
That was the adoption agency.
是领养管理处打来的。
And?
然后？
-We're getting a baby! -Are you serious?!
-我们可以领养孩子了！ -真的么？
There's a pregnant woman in Ohio, and she picked us.
有个俄亥俄州的孕妇选了我们！
-Oh, my God, that's great! -That's incredible.
-恭喜！真为你们高兴！ -太好了！
I'm so happy for you.
恭喜你们！
This Thanksgiving kicks last Thanksgiving's ass!
今年的感恩节比去年好太多了！
To Monica and Chandler and that knocked-up girl in Ohio.
敬莫尼卡和钱德 还有那俄亥俄州的小家伙！
I'm just so happy you guys are finally getting a kid.
你们两个终于有孩子了，这真让我高兴。
I know. Have you considered pageanting?
你们没考虑过怀孕么？
I can't believe they called. I mean, we're actually getting a baby.
他们打来电话，我们就会有孩子了 这真是不可思议！
I know how you feel.
我能体会你们的感受。
-Really? -Sure.
-真的么？ -当然啦
I went through the exact same thing with Alicia May Emory.
我以前经历过完全相同的事情。
The waiting, the wondering.
那种期待，那种迷茫
Then one day, I get that call from Toys "R" Us.
直到有一天 我从托伊那家店买到了那车！
She was in stock.
她又有货了！
That is the exact same thing.
确实“完全相同”。